{
    "subject": "Abel_Gance",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "La_Digue__film_",
    "human_readable": "Abel Gance directed the film La Digue.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8776352405548096,
            "question": "Who directed the film La Digue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8223239183425903,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Abel Gance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5757670402526855,
            "question": "What genre is the film La Digue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5400276184082031,
            "question": "When was the film La Digue released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5047568678855896,
            "question": "What was Abel Gance's filmmaking style like?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3335181176662445,
            "question": "How was La Digue received by critics and audiences upon its release?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3318711817264557,
            "question": "Is there a particular historical context surrounding the making of La Digue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3206395208835602,
            "question": "What are some notable themes explored in La Digue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31537026166915894,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors who appeared in La Digue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18629220128059387,
            "question": "What are some key visual elements or techniques used in La Digue?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Abel Gance directed the film La Digue.",
            "html": "yago_4164_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors who appeared in La Digue?",
            "html": "yago_4164_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some notable themes explored in La Digue?",
            "html": "yago_4164_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a particular historical context surrounding the making of La Digue?",
            "html": "yago_4164_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4164_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4164_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4164_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4164_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4164_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4164_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4164_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4164_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4164_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4164_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information supports the triple that Abel Gance directed the film La Digue. Specifically, the following documents confirm this fact:\n\n* `file_path`: `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_4164/re-ranker-msmarco/60.txt` ( mentions \"It was Gance's debut film\" referring to La Digue)\n* `file_path`: `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_4164/re-ranker-msmarco/64.txt` (mentions \"In 1911, with the help of friends, Gance formed a production company and directed his first film, La Digue\")\n* `file_path`: `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_4164/re-ranker-msmarco/28.txt` (mentions \"In 1911, with the help of friends, Gance formed a production company and directed his first film, La Digue\")"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Abel Gance, including that he directed the film \"La Digue\" in 1911. Therefore, the statement \"Abel Gance directed the film La Digue\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}